Take an unforgettable journey.
Finch is a science fiction, drama, adventure film directed by Miguel Sapochnik.
On a post-apocalyptic Earth, a robot, built to protect the life of his dying creator's
beloved dog, learns about life, love, friendship, and what it means to be human.
Finch, played by Tom Hanks.
Jeff (voice), played by Caleb Landry Jones.
Truck Driver (Flashback), played by Oscar Avila.
Mother (Flashback), played by Lora Martinez-Cunningham.
Daughter (Flashback), played by Marie Wagenman.
Warning System (voice), played by Emily Jones.
Finch is a 2021 American post-apocalyptic survival film directed by
Miguel Sapochnik and written by Craig Luck and Ivor Powell.
The film stars Tom Hanks and Caleb Landry Jones.
The story follows an aging man named Finch, a survivor in a nearly uninhabitable Earth,
who builds and teaches a robot to take care of his dog when he dies.
The film was announced as BIOS in October 2017.
Filming took place throughout New Mexico and in
Toronto from February to May 2019.
The film was scheduled to be released in theaters in the United States by Universal Pictures on
October 2, 2020, but was delayed several times due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
It was retitled Finch, sold to Apple TV+, and was released on November 5, 2021.
The film received lukewarm reviews from critics, with praise given to Hanks' performance, the visuals, and overall
charm, but criticism for its lack of originality and innovation within the post-apocalypse genre.
The film explores themes of post-apocalyptic future,
robot, taunting, questioning, journey.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.